More engrossing.
This story I raised on purpose.
I'm checking your footprints.
Don't tell me I'm being coy
Cause Love you Love you Love you
Jump for love
I'm late on purpose
The sympathetic song of Generation Z
I'm a deliberate bruising expert and a big buzzkill
Inari Tohoku-san
Sendai and the Tohoku region is energized
They are a 9-member idol group
You've got to check out S.M.S.
Now, on with the exchange.
This story is purposely uploaded.
We're checking your footsteps.
Hikaru Noritsuki, from Akita, has been with us since the group's inception in 2015, and is our oldest member at 21 years old.
He's currently located on that mountain.
I think I'm just now making a nice climb up the mountain.
About 6.5
We are aiming for the Pacifico Yokohama stage at the end of the year.
After that, we are aiming for the Budokan.
Who showed up at the lesson this day?
Good morning.
You came all the way to the squadron today.
Here we go.
Good morning, sir.
This is it. This is it.
Sorry, everyone is practicing.
Huh?
Do you remember?
I don't remember.
I'm Yaginuma from Afterforce.
Huh?
Hello.
Hello, I'm Yaginuma from Afterforce, and this is Yaginuma from Afterforce.
I'm Yaginuma of Afterforce.
Well, I'm going to tell you something important.
What?
Scary.
I'm scared.
What?
Scary, scary, scary.
Okay, everybody, ready?
Okay, yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes.
Letter of appointment!
I'll take off my mask.
Letter of appointment.
Mr. Northeast, suddenly.
Let's get you all out of here.
ABS Radio
I appoint you as
I appoint you as a monthly regular listener of ABS Radio Tamariba!
The name of the corner is suddenly Akita de Radiokko!
The radio corner is called "Akita Radio Kids" and it airs on Friday nights at 10:00 p.m. on ADS Radio.
In the corner, we will suddenly start a new corner for Tohoku products!
Please give us your best regards!
The members will visit Akita and talk on location, in the studio, and more!
I've always wanted to do this, and I've been saying for a long time that I wanted to do it. I've been saying I wanted to do this for a long time.
So I am really happy. I think my mother will be very happy.
I'm sure.
Are you watching?
I'm really nervous about being alone, but I love Akita so much,
I'm very happy because I'm going back to Iburi school and I'll be able to buy a lot of things to take home.
Yes, I am. I will grow up well.
I really love Akita, so I'm really excited and looking forward to visiting Akita on a regular basis.
I am really happy to have a regular program, so I will do my best to let everyone in Akita know about it. Please do your best.
I was surprised, wasn't I? I was surprised, but I really like Akita, as Tork-san has mentioned several times,
Every time I go to Akita, I feel more and more about Akita, and I really want to be there for everyone,
I hope that through this Tabariba, we will be able to learn more about Akita and its charms,
I hope we will be able to achieve something that we can deliver to you. I will do my best.
This is a very sudden and happy announcement, and I am feeling very happy right now.
I am looking forward to getting to know you all better through Radio Echo here in Akita today. I look forward to working with you.
I am always looking forward to the great future because Akita Broadcasting System has always taken care of me a lot and we can have an extraordinarily deep relationship in the future. I am looking forward to the future with great anticipation.
I am looking forward to the future.
I am a grandmother who makes babaherais.
undefined